Date Ordered: 2017/02/11 08:48:38 +0000
Job: j224616
Name: OpenStreetMap: London, England Metro Region
Data Listing Token: 2815bd74-644f-4426-9161-4c6deee48e88
Job Token: 1a172448-e22c-41e7-b744-3127c771bd08


### Contents of Data Order ###

# Data #
The Data folder contains the data that was ordered. The file extension depends on the type of data requested.

# Misc #
The Misc folder contains any additional information the provider included with the dataset. If the provider did not include any additional information, this folder will be empty.

# Description #
The Description File is a copy of the dataset's description as seen on the data listing when the data was ordered.

# Read Me #
The file you are currently reading.

# License #
The License agreement associated with the downloaded data. The license agreement contains information on use restrictions, liability, and disclaimers.